{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073389229","data":{"timestamp":" 947073389229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073389451","data":{"timestamp":" 947073389451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073390414","data":{"timestamp":" 947073390414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073391688","data":{"timestamp":" 947073391688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073394546","data":{"timestamp":" 947073394546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073395389","data":{"timestamp":" 947073395389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073395701","data":{"timestamp":" 947073395701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073396935","data":{"timestamp":" 947073396934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073400435","data":{"timestamp":" 947073400434"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073401418","data":{"timestamp":" 947073401418"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073401671","data":{"timestamp":" 947073401671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073402614","data":{"timestamp":" 947073402614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073405472","data":{"timestamp":" 947073405472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073406505","data":{"timestamp":" 947073406505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073406977","data":{"timestamp":" 947073406977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073411483","data":{"timestamp":" 947073411483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073411539","data":{"timestamp":" 947073411539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 0a5bd92c-1c84-46c6-b4bd-c4e1a29fc04b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073422727","data":{"timestamp":" 947073422726"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" ALICHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073426400","data":{"timestamp":" 947073426400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ALICHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALICHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073427960","data":{"timestamp":" 947073427960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" ANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073437354","data":{"timestamp":" 947073437354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073438962","data":{"timestamp":" 947073438962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" ANAOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073448202","data":{"timestamp":" 947073448202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073449808","data":{"timestamp":" 947073449807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" AKALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073454659","data":{"timestamp":" 947073454659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" AKALALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKALALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073456226","data":{"timestamp":" 947073456226"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073463870","data":{"timestamp":" 947073463870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANACHEZA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEZA"," userResponse":" ANACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073465499","data":{"timestamp":" 947073465499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073470148","data":{"timestamp":" 947073470148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANAKULA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073471729","data":{"timestamp":" 947073471729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073476119","data":{"timestamp":" 947073476119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073477715","data":{"timestamp":" 947073477715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073483150","data":{"timestamp":" 947073483149"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANASOMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073484794","data":{"timestamp":" 947073484793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073487586","data":{"timestamp":" 947073487585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANGUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGUKA"," userResponse":" ANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073489226","data":{"timestamp":" 947073489225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073492615","data":{"timestamp":" 947073492615"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ASALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASALI"," userResponse":" ASALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073494245","data":{"timestamp":" 947073494244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073496840","data":{"timestamp":" 947073496839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-A.rand.16__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073498873","data":{"timestamp":" 947073498872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073498967","data":{"timestamp":" 947073498967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073508247","data":{"timestamp":" 947073508247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 24cef80f-1016-4e8f-975f-090cee0325ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-A.rand.16__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ANDIKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073529414","data":{"timestamp":" 947073529413"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 6994aea9-3cd6-47e9-9b9b-01e6e23fcfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073543743","data":{"timestamp":" 947073543742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 6994aea9-3cd6-47e9-9b9b-01e6e23fcfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073552976","data":{"timestamp":" 947073552976"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 6994aea9-3cd6-47e9-9b9b-01e6e23fcfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073562279","data":{"timestamp":" 947073562279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 6994aea9-3cd6-47e9-9b9b-01e6e23fcfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073563614","data":{"timestamp":" 947073563614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 6994aea9-3cd6-47e9-9b9b-01e6e23fcfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073582966","data":{"timestamp":" 947073582966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 6994aea9-3cd6-47e9-9b9b-01e6e23fcfb0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073599330","data":{"timestamp":" 947073599330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073611639","data":{"timestamp":" 947073611639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073622047","data":{"timestamp":" 947073622047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073629248","data":{"timestamp":" 947073629248"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073638927","data":{"timestamp":" 947073638927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073649678","data":{"timestamp":" 947073649678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073650095","data":{"timestamp":" 947073650095"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073657920","data":{"timestamp":" 947073657920"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073669978","data":{"timestamp":" 947073669978"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073681721","data":{"timestamp":" 947073681721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073692180","data":{"timestamp":" 947073692180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073701458","data":{"timestamp":" 947073701458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073707617","data":{"timestamp":" 947073707617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1+2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073718858","data":{"timestamp":" 947073718858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073730605","data":{"timestamp":" 947073730605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073739398","data":{"timestamp":" 947073739397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 8a55415c-1a9d-4781-b6da-f8ce09c8cbf0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073751894","data":{"timestamp":" 947073751894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073770588","data":{"timestamp":" 947073770588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073775411","data":{"timestamp":" 947073775410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073798688","data":{"timestamp":" 947073798688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073808129","data":{"timestamp":" 947073808129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073810467","data":{"timestamp":" 947073810467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073834959","data":{"timestamp":" 947073834959"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073842063","data":{"timestamp":" 947073842063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" c1259bfc-b54d-4ee3-b097-6ca10951d1c3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073855251","data":{"timestamp":" 947073855250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073871971","data":{"timestamp":" 947073871971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073873558","data":{"timestamp":" 947073873557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073879327","data":{"timestamp":" 947073879327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073879426","data":{"timestamp":" 947073879426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEWE"," userResponse":" MKEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.we.rand.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073892077","data":{"timestamp":" 947073892076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_145609"," gameId":" 27556ee2-3314-42f2-9b07-056f8037ba4d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.we.rand.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mkewe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}